<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder" xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
    <ui:style>
    
    </ui:style>
    <g:HTMLPanel styleName="container">
    
    <g:Button ui:field="bottone2">Thank you</g:Button>
    <g:Button ui:field="bottone3">Welcome</g:Button>
    <g:Button ui:field="bottone4">iTunes Link</g:Button>
    <g:Button ui:field="bottone5">Ready to start</g:Button>
    
        <h1>Reflection.io</h1>
        <h2>Powerful market intelligence for the global app market.</h2>
        <p>Make smarter business decisions. Access revenue, download and rank data for any app in the store.</p>

        <h2>Features</h2>
        <p>We're launching soon with detailed revenue, rank and download data for apps on the iPhone and iPad stores.</p>

        <ul>
            <li>
                <h3>Revenue &amp; Download Data</h3>
                Analyse historical revenue, download and rank information for any app to base your business decisions on.
            </li>

            <li>
                <h3>Global App Leaderboard</h3>
                View revenue and download data for the Top 400 apps in any country, in any category, at any time.
            </li>

            <li>
                <h3>Powerful Statistical Model</h3>
                We have created an algorithm that statistically paints a very accurate picture of the stores based on public rank and
                private download and revenue
                data.
            </li>

            <li>
                <h3>Supported Stores</h3>
                We will launch with the iPhone and iPad stores and will then work hard to add all
                major stores starting with Google Play.
            </li>

            <li>
                <h3>Comprehensive Search</h3>
                Search for any app to see its revenue, download and rank history for any
                country and date range.
            </li>

            <li>
                <h3>Beautiful &amp; Functional</h3>
                Access meaningful market intelligence wherever you are on any device through our
                easy to use web app.
            </li>
        </ul>

        <h2>Make Smarter Decisions</h2>

        <p>Analyse daily revenue, downloads and rank for the Top 400 apps in any country &amp; category. Make smart business, marketing and development decisions
            by
            comparing the performance of similar apps.</p>

        <h2>About Us</h2>

        <p>We’re a core team of talented engineers and designers with over 35 years of combined experience in the web and mobile space.</p>

        <p>We were tired of how expensive and cumbersome it was to get up to date and accurate information about apps and the app market so we decided to create a
            better service ourselves.</p>

        <h3>Work with Reflection</h3>


        <p>Our small and passionate start-up is growing. If you're a self-starter, would love to be part of a growing start-up and have what it takes to get
            things done, we’d like to hear from you.</p>

        <ul>
            <li>
                <h3>William Shakour</h3>
                Originally from Sudan, William has written code for a large variety of devices and platforms - ranging from phones to servers and everything
                in-between. When he is not
                making sense of app data he loves to write mobile games.
            </li>
            <li>
                <h3>Gustaf Leksell</h3>
                Before founding Reflection, Gustaf led Business Development for Games at BBC Worldwide. He has lived and worked in Seoul, Shanghai and Austin
                where he designed &amp;
                produced successful mobile and online games.
            </li>
            <li>
                <h3>Chi Dire</h3>
                Chi has more than 20 years experience coding apps and services for small to global brands. With more than 600 apps across his devices, he thought
                it was time to
                try and make sense of it all.
            </li>
        </ul>

        <h2>Need data for reports or articles? Reference us and get it for free.</h2>

        <h2>Contact us</h2>

        <p>
            If you have any inquiries please get in touch using the form below, or send an email to
            <strong>hello at reflection.io</strong>
        </p>

        <ul>
            <li>
                <h3>Mail</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>hello at reflection.io</li>
                    <li>careers at reflection.io</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <h3>Location</h3>
                79 Wardour Street
                London, W1D 6QB.
            </li>
            <li>
                <h3>Contact</h3>
                +44 (0) 20 7851 8645
            </li>
            <li>
                <h3>Add us</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <a href="https://www.facebook.com/reflection.io" target="_blank">facebook</a>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <a href="http://www.linkedin.com/company/reflection-io-ltd" target="_blank">linkedIn</a>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 